♪ Music
♪ Music jah! I got a little bit of a... a little bit of a sore throat.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Are you okay?
Hanako, anyway, I'm going to be a mouthful today, MEME.
I ask my heart what's wrong I'm sure I won't know anything if I stay like this forever
of the brick time.
me spotlight, spotlight, spotlight... it's been a given since birth... the night before the music, it was really bad, and I wanted to fix it somehow.
I took some throat medicine and tried to speak in a whisper as much as possible.
But when I woke up in the morning, it was still bad as if there was no point.
I was really frustrated with my poor physical condition.
I will definitely, definitely fix it before the next camp.
I was afraid of what would happen if I just took it easy. I thought I would notice if it was true.
I wanted to cry. Tears fell.
I don't know. I'm not that sad.
I'm sure I wouldn't have wanted to notice it for a long, long time.
I'm telling you the truth. I'm asking my sad heart.
I can't go on like this forever.
The real me
I'll end this dark night not realizing how hard it is not realizing how hard it is not realizing how hard it is not realizing how hard it is not realizing how hard it is
I don't notice the hard things I don't notice the hard things
I don't notice the hard things I don't notice the hard things I don't notice the hard things
You don't notice the hard things
You don't notice the big things You don't notice the big things You don't notice the big things So let's not do it. So let's not do that.
Just get it together, okay? Okay. I see it in my young dreams, and I'm sure I've wanted to reach for it for a long, long time, and I'm sure I'm not the only one.
My unstoppable heart beats slowly on the side
I'm sure that if I don't keep going on like this forever
A song that hurts... my throat is still throbbing...
Ugh!
I can't sing... and I have a reputation to uphold
I want to sing, but I can't.
That's what I'm worried about
I've got some kind of reputation, and I want to sing, but I can't, and I'm worried about that.
I've actually given up on auditioning for anything, but I thought I could sing success, so I applied for it!
Thank you.
My voice again... I accidentally rang.
I accidentally squeaked a little yesterday.
Are you prone to losing your voice? What is it like when you tend to lose your voice? I have always been prone to voice dryness.
I tend to dry up quite easily.
That's why.
Anyway, today...
I feel like I'm going to have a "wishy-washy" day.
It's my body's biggest victory.
How much do you want to do by tomorrow?
I'm thinking...
I'll see how much I can cool it down.
So I'm going to use a hair cup to breathe in the steam.
or warm your throat as much as possible
I want you to take care of him as much as possible
Just a little bit.
There's a precedent.
He's under a lot of stress right now.
I'm so tired.
But it can't be helped,
I wonder what I can do to make up for it.
I'm going to try my best.
I'll do my best.
I think I'll be okay.
Yeah, I'll do my best. I love you. I love you. I love you.
If you don't have a voice, I don't think you're really going to be accepted.
I don't know what to do.
If I rest my voice until the final test
I'm still going to be different from everyone else.
I really, really, really hope that my throat will get better anyway.
I really, really, really, really
I really, really, really hope that my immune system is strong enough to handle it.
What do you think? Bread!
It's delicious.
It's good.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
How do you like it? Bread and you